Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG 42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-1988
  - David Hockney -- Press/Literature, 1978-1982 August (Box I:18, Folder 34)
  - David Hockney -- Sale Items, 1970-1977 (Box I:18, Folder 35)
  - American Stereographs -- Correspondence and Other Miscellaneous, 1980 May-September (Box I:18, Folder 36)
  - American Stereographs -- Fact Sheets, 1980 (Box I:18, Folder 37)
  - American Stereographs -- Press Releases, 1980 (Box I:18, Folder 38)
  - American Stereographs -- Publicity and Other Miscellaneous, 1979 April-1980 April (Box I:18, Folder 39)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide, Circa 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide (Braille), Circa 1979-1980 (Box I:18, Folder 41)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Audio Guide (Miscellaneous Research), Circa 1978-1980 (Box I:18, Folder 42)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Biographies, Circa 1978-1980 (Box I:18, Folder 43)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Background Material (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box I:19, Folder 1)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Background Material (2 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box I:19, Folder 2)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Deaf, 1982 April (Box I:19, Folder 3)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Fact Sheets, 1980 (Box I:19, Folder 4)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Press Releases, 1980 (Box I:19, Folder 5)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Publicity Mailing Lists, Circa 1978-1980 (Box I:19, Folder 6)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Reference on Handicapped, 1973 December-1981 May (Box I:19, Folder 7)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Research (1 of 2), 1976 August-1978 November (Box I:19, Folder 8)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Research (2 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box I:19, Folder 9)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Responses to Susan Cuddeback (Research), 1976 March-1979 April (Box I:19, Folder 10)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Robert Littman's File, 1976-1980 (Box I:19, Folder 11)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Sources of Information, Circa 1978-1980 (Box I:19, Folder 12)
  - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Susan Cuddeback Summary, 1979-1980 (Box I:19, Folder 13)
  - Sheldon Levison (Sept. 3-7, 1980), 1965-1980 (Box I:19, Folder 14)
  - Sheldon Levison -- Press Releases, 1980 August (Box I:19, Folder 15)
  - Grey Fall Schedule Press Release, 1980 (Box I:19, Folder 16)
  - Walter Gay -- Catalog, 1980 August-1982 February (Box I:19, Folder 17)
  - Walter Gay -- Press Literature, 1979 April-1981 January (Box I:19, Folder 18)
  - Walter Gay -- Research, 1978 February-1980 November (Box I:19, Folder 19)
  - Walter Gay -- Research Trip to Paris, 1979 October-December (Box I:19, Folder 20)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Background and Drafts, 1980 (Box I:19, Folder 21)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Boutique, 1977-1980 (Box I:19, Folder 22)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Lecture Series, 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 23)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Press Literature, 1979 December-1981 February (Box I:19, Folder 24)
  - Sonia Delaunay -- Robert Littman's File (Lists and Other Miscellaneous), Circa 1980 (Box I:19, Folder 25)
  - Advance Exhibit Schedule (Winter-Spring 1981), 1980 (Box I:19, Folder 26)
  - Court of Benin -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 27)
  - Court of Benin -- Press/Literature, 1980 April-1981January (Box I:19, Folder 28)
  - Italian Dwarings -- Long Island Tour, 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 29)
  - Italian Drawings -- Press, 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 30)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog, Circa 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 31)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog (John Myers Essay), Circa 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 32)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Correspondence, 1980 October-1981 July (Box I:19, Folder 33)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- John Myers Press/Literature, 1979 November-1981 July (Box I:19, Folder 34)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Press Release, 1981 (Box I:19, Folder 35)
  - Space Photography -- Book (1 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 36)
  - Space Photography -- Book (2 of 2), 1982 (Box I:19, Folder 37)
  - Space Photography -- Catalogue, 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 38)
  - Space Photography -- Catalogue and Other Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box I:19, Folder 39)
  - Photography of Space -- French Research, Circa 1980-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 40)
  - Space Photography -- Image Requests (JPL), 1981 January-June (Box I:19, Folder 41)
  - Space Photography -- Motorola, 1979-1982 May (Box I:19, Folder 42)
  - Photography of Space -- Note Cards, 1981 (Box I:19, Folder 43)
  - Space Photography -- Photo Captions, 1981 (Box I:19, Folder 44)
  - Space Photography -- Photos, 1981 January-April (Box I:19, Folder 45)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (1 of 3), 1976-1981 (Box I:19, Folder 46)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (2 of 3), 1979 August-1981 August (Box I:20, Folder 1)
  - Space Photography -- Press/Literature (3 of 3), 1979 December-1983 January (Box I:20, Folder 2)
  - Space Photography -- Press Release, 1981 June-December (Box I:20, Folder 3)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Advance and Press Release, 1981 (Box I:20, Folder 4)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz (Photo Copies), Circa 1980-1981 (Box I:20, Folder 5)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz (Gallatin Ass.), 1980-1983 (Box I:20, Folder 6)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Brademas Collection, 1981 (Box I:20, Folder 7)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Miscellaneous, 1976-1981 (Box I:20, Folder 8)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Planning and General Memos, 1980-1981 (Box I:20, Folder 9)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Ralph Fasanella, 1980-1981 (Box I:20, Folder 10)
  - Tanya Grosman (Small Gallery), 1981 April-1982 August (Box I:20, Folder 11)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Book Draft 2, Circa 1979-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 12)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Brochure, 1981 (Box I:20, Folder 13)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Catalog, 1981 (Box I:20, Folder 14)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Description of Exhibition, Circa 1979-1981 (Box I:20, Folder 15)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Installation Layout, CIrca 1980-1981 (Box I:20, Folder 16)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Pollock Beauborg Trip (Pompideau, France), 1981-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 17)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature (1 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 18)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature (2 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 19)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Works in Exhibition and Values, 1980 February-1981 June (Box I:20, Folder 20)
  - Ridiculous Theater, 1981 (Box I:20, Folder 21)
  - Chris Wilmarth (Exhibition Not Held), 1980 December-1981 December (Box I:20, Folder 22)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Bennington College, Circa 1980-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 23)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Final NYSCA Presentation (Visual Material), 1981-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 24)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Press Releases, Circa 1981-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 25)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Press Literature, 1978-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 26)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Catalog (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 27)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Catalog (2 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 28)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Press Releases, Circa 1981-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 29)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Audio Cassette (Ker-Seymer, Billy Chappell), 1980 July (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Check List for Photographs, Circa 1981-1982 (Box I:20, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Grey Press and Printed Material, 1985-1988 (Box I:20, Folder 32)
  - Stewart Wilson, 1981 (Box I:3, Folder 23)
  - Edward Henderson, 1981-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 24)
  - Around the Square (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box I:3, Folder 25)
  - Around the Square (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box I:3, Folder 26)
  - Around the Square -- Old Photographs and Curatorial Notes, circa 1980-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 27)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (1 of 3), 1980-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 28)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (2 of 3), 1980-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 29)
  - Around the Square -- Press/Literature (3 of 3), 1980-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 30)
  - Around the Square -- Correspondence, 1980 June-1982 June (Box I:3, Folder 31)
  - Around the Square -- Window Installations (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 32)
  - Around the Square -- Window Installations (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 33)
  - Around the Square -- Mindy Cantor, 1981 April-1982 October (Box I:3, Folder 34)
  - Around the Square -- Applebaum, 1981 December 3-1982 January 12 (Box I:3, Folder 35)
  - Around the Square -- Walking Tours, 1982 (Box I:3, Folder 36)
  - Around the Square -- PR Information, 1982 (Box I:3, Folder 37)
  - Bill Komosky, 1982 March-August (Box I:3, Folder 38)
  - Audubon -- Exhibition Research (Inquiries to Owners), 1981-1982 (Box I:3, Folder 39)
  - Audubon -- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box I:3, Folder 40)
  - John James Audubon and His Sons - Final NYSCA Presentation, 1982 March-May (Box I:3, Folder 41)
  - Audubon -- Magazine, 1982 January-February (Box I:3, Folder 42)
  - Audubon -- PR, 1982 January-1983 June (Box I:3, Folder 43)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Press Photos, 1982 (Box I:3, Folder 44)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Two Installations, 1982 April-June (Box I:3, Folder 45)
  - Hare/Kiesler -- Publicity/Biographical Information, 1979 February-1983 January (Box I:3, Folder 46)
  - Morse -- Packets of Reviews, 1982 July-1983 October (Box I:3, Folder 47)
  - Morse -- Promotion, 1982 July-1983 January (Box I:3, Folder 48)
  - Morse -- Photographs, 1982 June 17-1984 September 7 (Box I:3, Folder 49)
  - Morse -- Paul J. Strati, undated (Box I:3, Folder 50)
  - Morse -- Lectures and Gallery Talks, 1982 September-1983 March (Box I:3, Folder 51)
  - Morse -- Negatives of Text Labels, 1982-1983 (Box I:3, Folder 52)
  - Morse -- Works Not in Exhibition, 1982 August-1983 January (Box I:3, Folder 53)
  - Morse -- Paul Stati, 1980 November-1983 December (Box I:3, Folder 54)
  - Morse -- Benefit Preview, 1982 September (Box I:3, Folder 55)
  - Morse -- Benefit Opening and Viewing, 1982 August-September (Box I:3, Folder 56)
  - Morse -- Research, 1834-1872 (Box I:3, Folder 57)
  - Morse -- Correspondence, 1980 July-1984 March (Box I:3, Folder 58)
  - Faces -- Bob's File, 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 1)
  - Portrait Photography PR, 1982 August-November (Box I:4, Folder 2)
  - Face to Face, 1981 February-1983 January (Box I:4, Folder 3)
  - Faces Photographed, 1982 October-November (Box I:4, Folder 4)
  - Frida Kahlo Information, undated (Box I:4, Folder 5)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Publicity Photographs, undated (Box I:4, Folder 6)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Whitechapel Correspondence, 1981 October-1983 March (Box I:4, Folder 7)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- at Whitechapel Art Gallery, 1982 (Box I:4, Folder 8)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Labels, circa 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 9)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Catalog and Reproductions (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 10)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Catalog and Reproductions (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 11)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- General Correspondence, 1982 January-1983 September (Box I:4, Folder 12)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- PR (1 of 2), 1982 March-1983 October (Box I:4, Folder 13)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- PR (2 of 2), 1982 March-1983 October (Box I:4, Folder 14)
  - Bob's File -- Kahlo/Modotti, 1982 July-1983 January (Box I:4, Folder 15)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Press Release and Exhibition Description, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 16)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Review Packets, 1983 March-April (Box I:4, Folder 17)
  - Kahlo/Modotti -- Photographs, 1985 June-July (Box I:4, Folder 18)
  - Bergdorf/Montana Committee and Publicity, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 19)
  - Bob's Bergdorf/Montana, 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 20)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- AXIA, 1977-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 21)
  - Turkish Exhibition, 1979 March-1983 August (Box I:4, Folder 22)
  - Ottoman Show -- Label Copy, circa 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 23)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Items (1 of 2), circa 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 24)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Items (2 of 2), circa 1982-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 25)
  - Bob's File - TAT (Turkish Exhibit), 1982 July-1983 August (Box I:4, Folder 26)
  - Turkish Exhibition -- Object List from AIXA, 1982 December (Box I:4, Folder 27)
  - Ottoman Show and Reception PR and Invitation, 1982 December-1983 June (Box I:4, Folder 28)
  - Petropoulos Papers [Turkish Exhibition], 1983 April-1984 January (Box I:4, Folder 29)
  - Abby Weed Grey Exhibit -- Press Photos, circa 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 30)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Description, undated (Box I:4, Folder 31)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Correspondence, 1981 July-1984 March (Box I:4, Folder 32)
  - Paul Outerbridge -- Press, 1982 February-1983 October (Box I:4, Folder 33)
  - Eva Hesse -- Press and PR (1983), 1979-1983 (Box I:4, Folder 34)
  - Eva Hesse, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 35)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe Press, 1953-1983 December (Box I:4, Folder 36)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe Installation, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 37)
  - Louise Dahl -- Wolfe RRL File, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 38)
  - Dahl-Wolfe -- Interview, 1982 December 9 (Box I:4, Folder 39)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Interview (Cassette), 1982 December 9 (Box I:4, Folder 40)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Correspondence, 1982 May - 1983 September (Box I:4, Folder 41)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Dinner, 1983 August - September (Box I:4, Folder 42)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Magazine, 1981 June (Box I:4, Folder 43)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Staley-Wise Press Release, circa 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 44)
  - Permament Art Collection Exhibit, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 45)
  - Permanent Art Collection Exhibit -- Labels, 1983 (Box I:4, Folder 46)
  - Ken Tisa, 1983 November (Box I:4, Folder 47)
  - Picasso -- Hockney Essay, undated (Box I:4, Folder 48)
  - Picasso -- Schiff Essay, Undated (Box I:5, Folder 1)
  - Picasso -- Schiff, 1984 May-June (Box I:5, Folder 2)
  - Picasso -- Catalogue, 1983 (Box I:5, Folder 3)
  - Picasso -- Publications, 1983-1984 (Box I:5, Folder 4)
  - Picasso -- Press, 1983 June-November (Box I:5, Folder 5)
  - Picasso -- Proposal (Various Drafts), circa 1982-1983 (Box I:5, Folder 6)
  - Picasso -- Acknowledgements, circa 1982-1984 (Box I:5, Folder 7)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Krannert Art Museum, 1961 (Box I:5, Folder 8)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Exhibition, 1983 September-1984 June (Box I:5, Folder 9)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Installation, circa 1984 (Box I:5, Folder 10)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Bob's File, 1983 December-1984 March (Box I:5, Folder 11)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Correspondence to Newport Harbor, 1984 February-May (Box I:5, Folder 12)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Press; 1 of 2), 1979 June-1981 July (Box I:5, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Northern California Figs. (Press; 2 of 2), 1979 October-1984 July (Box I:5, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Painting -- North California Figs. (Correspondence), 1980 February-1984 January (Box I:5, Folder 15)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Joan Brown (Hansen Fuller Goldeen Gallery), 1978-1982 May (Box I:5, Folder 16)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Catalogue, 1984 January-March (Box I:5, Folder 17)
  - Bay Area Painting/Northern California Figs. -- Nathan Oliveira, 1980 (Box I:5, Folder 18)
  - Bay Area Painting/North California -- Action/Precision Catalogue, 1983-1984 January 25 (Box I:5, Folder 19)
  - Bay Area Painting -- Checklist, 1984 February-May (Box I:5, Folder 20)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, May 1983, After 1915 (Box I:5, Folder 21)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, May 1983(Littman and McCready), 1983 March-May (Box I:5, Folder 22)
  - Cocteau -- Invitation(Hill and Knowlton), Circa 1981-1984 (Box I:5, Folder 23)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (1 of 3), 1983 August-December (Box I:5, Folder 24)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (2 of 3), 1982 October-1983 August (Box I:5, Folder 25)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Correspondence (3 of 3), 1980 June-1982 November (Box I:5, Folder 26)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Parade Curtain, 1983 October-November (Box I:5, Folder 27)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Press, 1980 June-1984 November (Box I:5, Folder 28)
  - Cocteau -- Literature, 1984 February-November (Box I:5, Folder 29)
  - Jean Cocteau-- RRL File, 1981-1983 (Box I:5, Folder 30)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Summary, 1984 March-November (Box I:5, Folder 31)
  - Cocteau -- Catalogue, Circa 1983-1984 (Box I:5, Folder 32)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Press Material (1 of 2), 1948 November-1984 July (Box I:5, Folder 33)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Press Material (2 of 2), 1965 (Box I:5, Folder 34)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Installation and Gallery Reception, 1984 July (Box I:5, Folder 35)
  - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Invitation, 1984 June-August (Box I:5, Folder 36)
  - Boldini -- Photographs (Poster), 1984 (Box I:5, Folder 37)
  - Boldini -- Photographs, 1984 (Box I:5, Folder 38)
  - Boldini -- Catalogue, 1984 November (Box I:5, Folder 39)
  - Boldini -- Catalogue, 1984 (Box I:5, Folder 40)
  - Boldini Giovanni (November 13-December 22, 1984), 1984 October-1985 April (Box I:5, Folder 41)
  - Action/Precision -- Al Held, 1982 (Box I:5, Folder 42)
  - Action/Precision -- Reviews, 1984 June-1985 January (Box I:5, Folder 43)
  - Action/Precision -- Invitation, 1984 December-1985 January (Box I:5, Folder 44)
  - Action/Precision -- Press Photos, 1984 December-1985 January (Box I:5, Folder 45)
  - Action/Precision -- Information and Press, 1984 December-1985 January (Box I:5, Folder 46)
  - Action/Precision -- Press Release, 1984 June-December (Box I:5, Folder 47)
  - Action/Precision -- Symposium Tape, 1985 January-1986 September (Box I:5, Folder 48)
  - Precious -- Exhibit, 1985 February-September (Box I:5, Folder 49)
  - Precious -- Correspondence, 1984 December-1985 May (Box I:5, Folder 50)
  - Precious -- Images and Conditions, Circa 1985 (Box I:5, Folder 51)
  - Precious -- Press(1 of 2), 1985 March-September (Box I:5, Folder 52)
  - Precious -- Press(2 of 2), 1986 January-June (Box I:6, Folder 1)
  - Precious -- Catalogue and Notes, Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 2)
  - Precious -- Artist Resumes, Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 3)
  - Precious -- Bibliography, 1981 December-1985 March (Box I:6, Folder 4)
  - Precous -- Photos and Transparencies, Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 5)
  - Labyrinth -- Press, 1984 August-1985 May (Box I:6, Folder 6)
  - Labyrinth -- Catalogue, Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 7)
  - Labyrinth -- Gaudnek Catalogue, 1977 (Box I:6, Folder 8)
  - Labyrinth -- Correspondence, 1984 November-1985 May (Box I:6, Folder 9)
  - Labyrinth -- Miscellaneous, 1984 November-1985 November (Box I:6, Folder 10)
  - Alfredo Jaar -- Installation Projects, 1980-1985, Undated (Box I:6, Folder 11)
  - Sol LeWitt -- Background Material and Press, 1984 November-1985 February (Box I:6, Folder 12)
  - Sol LeWitt -- Press Releases, Reviews and Photos, 1985 June-1986 March (Box I:6, Folder 13)
  - Sol LeWitt -- Correspondence, 1985 January-1987 (Box I:6, Folder 14)
  - Sol LeWitt -- Miscellaneous, 1974 July-1986 March (Box I:6, Folder 15)
  - Indelible Image -- Press Photos, 1860s-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 16)
  - Indelible Image -- Photograph Copies, 1840s-1970s (Box I:6, Folder 17)
  - Indelible Image -- War Photography, 1968 January-1985 March (Box I:6, Folder 18)
  - Indelible Image -- Press Release, 1985 September (Box I:6, Folder 19)
  - Indelible Image -- Reviews, 1985 September-1986 April (Box I:6, Folder 20)
  - Indelible Image -- Study Guide Draft (1 of 2), Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 21)
  - Indelible Image -- Study Guide Draft (2 of 2), Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 22)
  - Indelible Image -- Study Guide(1 of 2), 1985 (Box I:6, Folder 23)
  - Indelible Image --Study Guide(2 of 2), 1985 (Box I:6, Folder 24)
  - Indelible Image -- Notes for Symposium (Thomas Sokolowski), Circa 1984-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 25)
  - Josef Schutzenhofer Drawings -- Small Gallery(War Photography), 1985 May-November (Box I:6, Folder 26)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Artists' Correspondence, 1985 August-1986 April (Box I:6, Folder 27)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Artists, Circa 1985-1986 (Box I:6, Folder 28)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Herwitz Correspondence, 1984 October-1986 December (Box I:6, Folder 29)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Other Indian Artists (Non-Exhibition), Circa 1974-1985 (Box I:6, Folder 30)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Press Release, 1985 June-December (Box I:6, Folder 31)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Festival of India Press, 1984 July-1985 September (Box I:6, Folder 32)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Reviews and Press Coverage, 1985 October-1987 March (Box I:6, Folder 33)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Phillips/Herwitz Collection, 1985-1986 (Box I:6, Folder 34)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Thomas Sokolowski Lecture, 1986 January 9 (Box I:6, Folder 35)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Dartmouth Exhibition, 1985 August-1986 March (Box I:6, Folder 36)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- List of Works and Slides Borrowed, 1985 (Box I:6, Folder 37)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Catalogue Master Printout, Circa 1985-1986 (Box I:6, Folder 38)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Catalogue Drafts, Circa 1985-1986 (Box I:6, Folder 39)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Drafts, Circa 1985-1986 (Box I:6, Folder 40)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Errata Page, Circa 1985-1986 (Box I:6, Folder 41)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Miscellaneous, 1984 July-1985 December (Box I:6, Folder 42)
  - Modern Redux -- List of Architects, 1985 October (Box I:6, Folder 43)
  - Modern Redux -- List of Architects (Cards), Undated (Box I:6, Folder 44)
  - Modern Redux -- Proposal, 1985 June-October (Box I:6, Folder 45)
  - Modern Redux -- Architects, Works Lists and Douglas Davis Proposal, Undated (Box I:6, Folder 46)
  - Modern Redux -- Press Release, 1986 (Box I:6, Folder 47)
  - Modern Redux -- Responses from Architects, 1985 January-1986 May (Box I:6, Folder 48)
  - Modern Redux -- Addendum, Undated (Box I:7, Folder 1)
  - Modern Redux -- Wall Texts, Undated (Box I:7, Folder 2)
  - Modern Redux -- Letters to Architects, 1985 August-1986 January (Box I:7, Folder 3)
  - Modern Redux -- Reviews, 1986 June-October (Box I:7, Folder 4)
  - Modern Redux -- Miscellaneous, 1983-1986 June (Box I:7, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin and His Circle -- Invitation List, Undated (Box I:7, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin and His Circle -- Press Release, 1986 March-April (Box I:7, Folder 7)
  - A.E. Gallatin and His Circle -- Reviews, 1986 June 13 (Box I:7, Folder 8)
  - Abstract Appropriations, 1986 (Box I:7, Folder 9)
  - Rosalyn Drexler -- Notes, 1985-1986 (Box I:7, Folder 10)
  - Rosalyn Drexler -- Notes, 1986 (Box I:7, Folder 11)
  - Rosalyn Drexler -- Publicity, 1986 July-November (Box I:7, Folder 12)
  - Rosalyn Drexler -- Press Release, 1986 June (Box I:7, Folder 13)
  - Rosalyn Drexler -- Catalogue, 1986 (Box I:7, Folder 14)
  - Rosalyn Drexler -- Miscellaneous, Circa 1985-1986 (Box I:7, Folder 15)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Press Release, 1986 June (Box I:7, Folder 16)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Publicity, 1986 July (Box I:7, Folder 17)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Paintings 1940-1985 (Catalogue), 1986 (Box I:7, Folder 18)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Catalogue (1 of 2), 1986 April-May (Box I:7, Folder 19)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Catalogue (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box I:7, Folder 20)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Questions, 1985 October-1989 August (Box I:7, Folder 21)
  - Ruth Abrams -- Miscellaneous, 1986 March-April (Box I:7, Folder 22)
  - Arnulf Rainer -- C.V., Undated (Box I:7, Folder 23)
  - Arnulf Rainer -- Press Release, 1986 August (Box I:7, Folder 24)
  - Arnulf Rainer -- Self Portraits (September 8-October 25, 1986), 1986 July-September (Box I:7, Folder 25)
  - Arnulf Rainer -- Press Reviews, 1986 September-1988 February (Box I:7, Folder 26)
  - Arnulf Rainer -- Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box I:7, Folder 27)
  - Simon Linke -- Paintings (Small Gallery in Conjunction with Rainer), 1986 July (Box I:7, Folder 28)
  - Claudia de Monte -- Window Display, 1985-1986 (Box I:7, Folder 29)